ELEFTHERIOS MOSCHOS

PROJECT MANAGER & FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

***** +61 400 079 794

18 Price St, Thevenard SA

EDUCATION

University of Adelaide

Master of Project Management Full-Stack Flex Program

TAFE and Further Studies

Advanced Diploma of Project Management

Certificate III Mechanical (Heavy Mobile Equipment Plant/Earth Moving/Agricultural)

Immanuel College

SACE – Year 12

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Large-scale project management

Full-Stack Web Development Maintenance management

KPI tracking/reporting

Growth strategy planning/implementation

Project-team leadership

Experienced in highly-regulated industries

Various accreditation and courses relating to industry demands – provided on request

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

- GRA Scholarship
- TSCC President 3 years
- Project Lead MODU Jack Bates Major Project

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Project manager in the web development space leveraging studies with a master's in applied project management and full-stack web development both completed through the University of Adelaide. Extensive experience delivering projects across differing industries that provide business value from maintenance management system development and implementation to major asset construction projects. With newly formed skills and understanding of front-end and back-end web development technologies I am in endless pursuit of delivering web projects that have purpose and deliver real value not only to the business but to those that use them.

Offering a unique perspective from previous experience in projects and passion for digital technologies I'm well positioned to apply my strengths in team collaboration, stakeholder management and real world problem-solving to the benefit of the organisation.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2020 – Current / Full-Stack Flex Program - University of Adelaide Full-Stack Web Developer

- Building front-end web applications utilising HTML5, CSS and JavaScript in conjunction with frameworks and libraries such JQuery, Bootstrap, Bulma etc
- 3rd Party API integration with AJAX
- Building Back-end application utilising node.js, express.js, mySQL, Heroku in conjunction with frameworks and NPM packages such Sequelize, Inquirer, Jest and many others.
- Managing projects ustilising Git and GitHub version control
- Working in remote project teams with Zoom and Slack.

2016 – Current / Gypsum Resources Australia Mining Project Manager/Asset and Maintenance Supervisor

- Manager for GRA Maintenance Management System Project
- Establish new procedures and standards for maintenance management; moving to a computerised system
- Develop, implement and evaluate KPI's
- Ensure statutory and regulatory compliance
- Build strong teams

2016 – Current / Thevenard sports and Community Centre Club President

- Manage all aspect of the TSCC business and finances
- Plan, organise and carry out responsibilities associated with role
- Liaise with committee, staff and members
- Chair club committee meetings
- Support club members

ELEFTHERIOS MOSCHOS (TERRY)

PROJECT MANAGER & MAINTENANCE SPECIALIST

CONTACT

+61 400 079 794

18 Price St, Thevenard SA

REFEREES

Provided on request

2009 -2015 / Transocean Sedco Forex Aust – Offshore Drilling Maintenance/Mechanical Supervisor & Jack Bates Project PIC

- Development of Project scope within budget and timeline
- Build professional rapport with senior management to ensure timely and affective decision making
- Liaise with third party contractors
- Ensure compliance to quality and risk control measures
- Execute shipyard mechanical work to company standards
- Ensure accuracy of maintenance and equipment reports
- Mentor and develop crew members

2008 -2009 / Transocean Sedco Forex Intl. – Offshore Drilling Rig Mechanic / Chief Mechanic – Singapore Base

- Commission mechanical equipment for shipyard projects
- Implement mechanical, pneumatic and hydraulic installations
- Ensure compliance to quality and risk control measures
- Ensure accuracy and completion of operational reports

2006 – 2008 / Hunter Energy and Mineral Co.

Senior Rig Mechanic

- 24/hr on-call, stand-alone mechanic on FIFO roster
- Work and maintain a safe working environment
- Maintain and repair hydraulic power equipment and pneumatic equipment
- Lead and manage maintenance teams
- Provide daily reports to senior management

2003 – 2007 / Ceduna Machinery Pty Ltd.

Diesel Mechanic

- Knowledge of and experience with earth moving, agricultural and commercial vehicles
- Repair and service engines
- Adhere to a safe work environment
- Prioritise work schedule in responding to consumers